September Blue, thy sorrows be forgotten
九月之靛，汝之憂被淡忘
October Auburn, let this season pass
十月之紅，讓這季節過去
November Gray, restore with thy rain
十一之灰，以汝雨水恢復
December White, thy beauty ever last
十二之白，汝之美永留存
Light of virtue shown
美德之光高照
Sign of one's true form
接露人之本面
To grow, only small
一點一滴教育
Giving guidance for all
引領世間萬物
Seen while hardly known
有誰能真正看懂
September Blue, thy sorrows be forgotten
九月之靛，汝之憂被淡忘
October Auburn, let this season pass
十月之紅，讓這季節過去
November Gray, restore with thy rain
十一之灰，以汝雨水恢復
December White, thy beauty ever last
十二之白，汝之美永留存
Bright inviting morn
和藹的那道晨光
Brilliant rays reborn
閃耀的光芒再現
So follow along
跟上腳步
as the shadows have gone
黑夜已成明日
Walk where time has torn
跟我穿越時空
September Blue, thy sorrows be forgotten
九月之靛，汝之憂被淡忘
October Auburn, let this season pass
十月之紅，讓這季節過去
November Gray, restore with thy rain
十一之灰，以汝雨水恢復
December White, thy beauty ever last
十二之白，汝之美永留存
December White
十二之白
(December White)
(十二之白)
Thy beauty ever last
汝之美永留存
(Thy beauty ever last)
(汝之美永留存)